Department of Chemistry Records UA151
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Undergraduate Theses, 1910 -- 1967; UA151.001; 10.8 Linear Feet
  - The action of allyl bromide, of ethyl iodoacetate, and of para anisyl isothiocyanate on sodium phenylacetylene, 1926; UA151.001.004.00175; Rouillard, Whitman G. (Box 4)
  - Condensation of nitromethane and benzaldehyde to nitrostyrol, with the aid of organic catalysts, 1926; UA151.001.004.00176; Synkovich, Frank C. (Box 4)
  - Manufacture and purification of zinc sulphate, 1926; UA151.001.004.00177; Thomas, C. F. (Box 4)
  - An investigation of peroxide fusions for tin ores, 1926; UA151.001.004.00178; Turner, Charles (Box 4)
  - The preparation of nitro-styrene by an improved method, 1926; UA151.001.004.00179; Weisberg, S. M. (Box 4)
  - The synthesis of hydratropic aldehyde, 1927; UA151.001.004.00180; Crawford, Kenneth Malcolm (Box 4)
  - Sulphur in wood, 1927; UA151.001.004.00181; Hutchinson, Doris R. (Box 4)
  - The separation of pure para-xylene from technical para-xylene, 1927; UA151.001.004.00182; Johnson, Raymond L. (Box 4)
  - Chromium plating with aqueous solutions of organic compounds, 1927; UA151.001.004.00183; Lawson, Herbert E. Jr. (Box 4)
  - The condensation of meta substituted benzaldehydes with nitro methane, 1927; UA151.001.004.00184; McCarthy, Edith Marie (Box 4)
  - A report on the effect of solid mediums such as sand, sphalerite, ground glass, or rotten rock on the rate of diffusion, 1927; UA151.001.004.00185; Pierce, William M. (Box 4)
  - The quantitative determination of antimony when arsenic is present, 1927; UA151.001.004.00186; Platts, Braman Boyd (Box 4)
  - The extraction of lead from scrap storage battery metal, 1927; UA151.001.004.00187; Reddie, J. Wallace (Box 4)
  - Paratolisothiocyanate as a reagent in the detection of alcohols, 1927; UA151.001.004.00188; Roesch, Esther M. (Box 4)
  - Reaction of unsaturated 1:4 diketones, 1927; UA151.001.004.00189; Rosener, Harry B. (Box 4)
  - Preparation of methoxyacetic acid and preparation of trimethylene chlorohydrin, 1928; UA151.001.004.00190; Bicknell, Laurence A. (Box 4)
  - Preparation of methoxyacetonitrile and reaction of phenylnitromethane on b-chlorpropiophenone, 1928; UA151.001.004.00191; Bridgess, M. Philbrick (Box 4)
  - An apparatus for determining the specific heat of solutions, 1928; UA151.001.004.00192; Carter, Merrill J. (Box 4)
  - The action of certain aromatic chlorides on di-ethyl-sodium-isothioanilido-methane-tri-carboxalate, 1928; UA151.001.004.00193; Cook, Philip G. (Box 4)
  - An investigation of the change in hydrogen ion concentration of a clock reaction, 1928; UA151.001.004.00194; Coyle, Theodore R. (Box 4)
  - The reaction of acetylacetone with certain aryl mustard oils, 1928; UA151.001.004.00195; Gesner, Ethel M. (Box 4)
  - A study of some derivatives of dibenzylamine, 1928; UA151.001.004.00196; Hanslick, Roy Stanley (Box 4)
  - A study of "Doctor" solution as used in gasoline refining, 1928; UA151.001.004.00197; Hapgood, Kenneth B. (Box 4)
  - The action of butyl magnesium bromide on para ethoxy phenyl isothiocyanate. The action of butyl magnesium bromide on methyl mustard oil, 1928; UA151.001.004.00198; Marsh, Louise Gardener (Box 4)
  - Grignard reagent and aliphatic mustard oils. Sodium aceto acetic ester and aliphatic mustard oils, 1928; UA151.001.004.00199; Minichiello, Michael J. (Box 4)
  - Some reactions of phenyl mustard oil, 1928; UA151.001.004.00200; Siegel, Mark (Box 4)
  - History and synthesis of adrenalin, 1928; UA151.001.004.00201; Tishler, Max (Box 4)
  - The addition of benzyl cyanide to methyl cinnamate, 1928; UA151.001.004.00202; Welch, Walter F. Jr. (Box 4)
  - An investigation of the change in hydrogen-ion concentration and oxidation - reduction potentials of the arsenate - thiosulfate clock reaction, 1929; UA151.001.004.00203; Casellini, E. Thomas (Box 4)
  - Bromination of desylacetophenone, 1929; UA151.001.004.00204; Herrman, Ernest F. (Box 4)
  - Diacyl styrenes, 1929; UA151.001.004.00205; Hubbard, John R. (Box 4)
  - Preparation and oxidation of the anilide of benzalacetophenone. Preparation of methoxyacetonitrile. Preparation of methoxyacetophenone., 1929; UA151.001.004.00206; Irvin, A. M. (Box 4)
  - Floating a zinc ore, 1929; UA151.001.004.00207; Karklin, E. Fred (Box 4)
  - Sugar analysis, 1929; UA151.001.004.00208; Manikian, Jerayr (Box 4)
  - An investigation into the relation between the density and analysis of Swedish Kolmn, 1929; UA151.001.004.00209; Miller, Don A. (Box 4)
  - The preparation of the 4-halogen derivatives of diphenyl, 1929; UA151.001.004.00210; Phillips, Ralph A. (Box 4)
  - The electro-chemical method for determining pH values of some common substances, 1929; UA151.001.004.00211; Sjostrom, Augusta M. (Box 4)
  - The preparation of standards for the colorimetric determination of hydrogen ion concentrations, 1929; UA151.001.004.00212; Smith, Eunice M. (Box 4)
  - Preparation and properties of p-bromdiphenyl methyl ketone, 1929; UA151.001.004.00213; Stone, Dorothy L. (Box 4)
  - The influence of pH on plating solutions, 1929; UA151.001.004.00214; Wetherbee, Burton W. (Box 4)
  - Preparation and properties of diphenyl arsenic acid, 1930; UA151.001.004.00215; Bergin, Ursula Shaw (Box 4)
  - The iodometric determination of copper, 1930; UA151.001.004.00216; Boardman, Charles E. (Box 4)
  - The synthesis of ketones from acid anhydrides, 1930; UA151.001.004.00217; Brown, Gordon (Box 4)
  - The conductivity of aqueous solutions of glycerol and boric acid, 1930; UA151.001.004.00218; Burdett, Marion (Box 4)
  - A study of metallographical methods, 1930; UA151.001.004.00219; Currier, E. A. (Box 4)
  - The determination of antimony quantitatively in the presence of arsenic, 1930; UA151.001.004.00220; Mann, Charles V. (Box 4)
  - The application of the animony electrode in determining the alkalinity of silver plating solutions, 1930; UA151.001.004.00221; Orr, Malcolm A. (Box 4)
  - A study of the reductor-permanganate process for the determination of phosporus in cast iron and a rapid non-filter method for the determination of phosphorus in cast iron and steel, 1930; UA151.001.004.00222; Russell, Henry F. (Box 4)
  - A study in the pyrazolone series, 1931; UA151.001.004.00223; Deutsch, Emmanuel (Box 4)
  - Acid compounds in baking powders and the determination of their speeds of reaction, 1931; UA151.001.004.00224; Fedor, Ruth (Box 4)
  - Preparation and properties of tertiary butyl amine (CH3)3CNH2, 1931; UA151.001.005.00225; Foust, Orville N. (Box 5)
  - The addition of sodium acetoacetic esters to the aliphatic mustard oils, 1931; UA151.001.005.00226; Hoisington, Sumner J. (Box 5)
  - A study of certain dyestuffs on silk, 1931; UA151.001.005.00227; Lupien, Frank U. (Box 5)
  - The recovery of lead from storage battery plate scrap, 1931; UA151.001.005.00228; MacCuspie, Norman E. (Box 5)
  - 2, 4 dinitrochlorbenzene; 2, 4 dinitrobrombenzene 2, 4 dinitroiodobenzene and the Friedel-Crafts Reaction, 1931; UA151.001.005.00229; Maclaren, Stanley F. M. (Box 5)
  - Analysis of petrified wood, 1931; UA151.001.005.00230; Murphy, Anna J. (Box 5)
  - Studies in the biphenyl series: tri-ortho-biphenyl-phosphine, 1931; UA151.001.005.00231; Perlman, David E. (Box 5)
  - The preparation and decomposition of pure paraperiodic acid, 1931; UA151.001.005.00232; Pender, Mildred J. (Box 5)
  - Preparation of ortho tri-biphenylstibine, 1931; UA151.001.005.00233; Wolf, Arthur (Box 5)
  - Preparation of tribiphenylarsine, 1931; UA151.001.005.00234; Yeaton, Raymond A. (Box 5)
  - Beryllium and compounds, 1932; UA151.001.005.00235; Biog, Fletcher S. (Box 5)
  - An investigation of an antimony amalgam electrode, 1932; UA151.001.005.00236; Fearns, Edward C. (Box 5)
  - Application of the electron tube voltmeter to the determination of copper, 1932; UA151.001.005.00237; Fox, Clifford P. (Box 5)
  - Some organic compounds of phosphorus, 1932; UA151.001.005.00238; Geary, Charles G. (Box 5)
  - Investigation of the reaction TiO2+Mg for metallic titanium in the product, 1932; UA151.001.005.00239; Sackett, Ernest D. (Box 5)
  - Preparation of nitromethane, 1932; UA151.001.005.00240; Tuttle, Lewis C. (Box 5)
  - A study of cativa resin, 1932; UA151.001.005.00241; Wilcox, Ross C. (Box 5)
  - The preparation and properties of p-bismuth tribiphenyl, 1933; UA151.001.005.00242; Bidgood, Earle S. (Box 5)
  - Violet ultramarine and composition, 1933; UA151.001.005.00243; Blackburn, Newell F. (Box 5)
  - The removal of antimony and copper from lead, 1933; UA151.001.005.00244; Bretscher, Milton H. (Box 5)
  - Design of vacuum tube voltmeter and its application for the determination of pH, 1933; UA151.001.005.00245; Giesecke, Paul (Box 5)
  - Preparation of, and dyes from, tetramethyl-diamino-diphenyl-furyl methane, 1933; UA151.001.005.00246; Keyes, Mabel A. (Box 5)
  - Chemical analysis of several wells in West Boxford Mass. to determine their suitability for domestic consumption, 1933; UA151.001.005.00247; McGregor, Marion C. (Box 5)
  - Determination of acetyl values, 1933; UA151.001.005.00248; Miller, Ralph B. (Box 5)
  - The anaylsis of gelatine solutions by viscosity measurements and determination of the iso-electric point, 1933; UA151.001.005.00249; Portman, Eli (Box 5)
  - Preparation of desoxybenzoin, 1933; UA151.001.005.00250; Rooney, Raymond (Box 5)
  - The preparation and reactions of p-diethyl amino diphenyl, 1933; UA151.001.005.00251; Turok, Max (Box 5)
  - A study of the preparation and properties of triphenyl methane dyes, 1933; UA151.001.005.00252; Vermette, Paul D. (Box 5)
  - The separation of arsenic from animony solutions about to be titrated, 1933; UA151.001.005.00253; Wortman, Weldon W. (Box 5)
  - The preparation of compounds similiar to adrenaline, 1934; UA151.001.005.00254; Branca, Joseph T. (Box 5)
  - The preparation of carotene from fresh carrots, 1934; UA151.001.005.00255; Carey, Raymond J. (Box 5)
  - The preparation of glutamic acid and the study of Knoevenagel's Reaction through use of a secondary amine, 1934; UA151.001.005.00256; Clair, John P. (Box 5)
  - A synthesis of beta, beta di-normal propylmalic acid beta lactone, 1934; UA151.001.005.00257; Coughlan, Ruth G. (Box 5)
  - Studies in biphenyl series synthesis of allyl biphenyl, 1934; UA151.001.005.00258; Jeveli, Edmund S. (Box 5)
  - Synthesis of n-heptadecylamine, 1934; UA151.001.005.00259; Johnston, Donald O. (Box 5)
  - Knoevenagle's Reaction: The condensation of butyric aldehyde with acetone, 1934; UA151.001.005.00260; MacNeil, Jane G. (Box 5)
  - Sulphonation of alcohols (cetyl and olein), 1934; UA151.001.005.00261; McFarlane, A. N. (Box 5)
  - Synthesis of alpha-dithio-naphthoic acid, 1934; UA151.001.005.00262; McGowan, Frank L. (Box 5)
  - Study of the preparation of ionone, 1934; UA151.001.005.00263; Racich, Margaret M. (Box 5)
  - A study of phenol-formaldehyde resins, 1934; UA151.001.005.00264; Saracco, Francis P. (Box 5)
  - Preparation of 1, 4-dibenzoylbutane, 1934; UA151.001.005.00265; Thompson, Martha M. (Box 5)
  - Synthesis of mehylene di barbituric acid sodium and synthesis of phenyl benzoin and its action on the arsenomolybdic acid reagent, 1935; UA151.001.005.00266; Bradway, C. J. (Box 5)
  - Study of the ester formation of cinnamic acid, 1935; UA151.001.005.00267; Coville, Dorothy M. (Box 5)
  - The age of wilberforce uraninite by the analytical determination of lead, uranium, and thorium, 1935; UA151.001.005.00268; Hurwitz, Gilmore (Box 5)
  - The decomposition of potassium chlorate, 1935; UA151.001.005.00269; Lawrence, Raymond B. (Box 5)
  - The synthesis of thyroxine, 1935; UA151.001.005.00270; Levine, Irving M. (Box 5)
  - Some reactions of cyanamid, 1935; UA151.001.005.00271; Losco, F. A. (Box 5)
  - The bromination of benzil by direct methods, 1935; UA151.001.005.00272; Lupien, Donald F. (Box 5)
  - A study of the action of water on raney alloys, 1935; UA151.001.005.00273; Simon, Simon (Box 5)
  - Preparation and properties of cystine, 1935; UA151.001.005.00274; Swanson, Dorothy (Box 5)
  - A study of metalographical technique, 1936; UA151.001.005.00276; Buckle, George Flett (Box 5)
  - Preparation and relative sweetness of tri-chloro, tri-bromo, and mono and di-iodo acetamides, and an attempt to prepare tri-iodo acetamide, 1936; UA151.001.005.00277; Buckley, William R. (Box 5)
  - The preparation of butyl derivatives of diethylene glycol, 1936; UA151.001.005.00278; Di Tomaso, Antonio (Box 5)
  - The chemical and microscopical investigation of textile fibres and fabrics, 1936; UA151.001.005.00279; Hansen, Edwin Russell (Box 5)
  - Sulfonation of olive oil, 1936; UA151.001.005.00280; Shiere, Howard B. (Box 5)
  - The preparation of lead bismuth alloys and a study in metallography, 1937; UA151.001.005.00281; Brennan, Humphrey C. (Box 5)
  - Testing the validity and application of the Freundlich Isotherm in relation to the adsorptive properties of charcoal in solution, 1937; UA151.001.006.00282; Carey, J. F. (Box 6)
  - Relation between the size of the particle, resulting from the Fehling's solution test of sugars, and the wavelength it reflects or refracts, 1937; UA151.001.006.00283; Carey, J. F. (Box 6)
  - Metallography, 1937; UA151.001.006.00284; Duffy, George J. (Box 6)
  - Cellulose and its acetyl derivative, 1937; UA151.001.006.00285; Jafarian, Ethel (Box 6)
  - Preparation of 2':3' diphenylindoles from benzoin and primary benzenoid amines, 1937; UA151.001.006.00286; Keith, Roger S. (Box 6)
  - Analysis of gas mixtures by thermal conductivity, 1937; UA151.001.006.00287; Levine, Aaron (Box 6)
  - The determination of the thermoelectric power of simple alloy systems, 1937; UA151.001.006.00288; Livingston, William M. (Box 6)
  - The oxidation of tribromaniline, 1937; UA151.001.006.00289; Manning, Joseph F. (Box 6)
  - A study of adsorption by inorganic substances, 1937; UA151.001.006.00290; McGowan, Louis E. (Box 6)
  - Condensations with the sodium derivative of phenylacetylene, 1937; UA151.001.006.00291; Morgan, Edwin Jr. (Box 6)
  - Preparation of Hansa Yellow G, and synthesis of related dyes, 1937; UA151.001.006.00292; Ober, Henry W. Jr. (Box 6)
  - Construction of a gas fired annealing furnace and a study of metallography, 1937; UA151.001.006.00293; Redshaw, Lincoln L. (Box 6)
  - Experiments on electro plating of tungsten, 1937; UA151.001.006.00294; Silbovitz, Samuel (Box 6)
  - The determination of the presence of water of crystallization in hydromagma paste, 1937; UA151.001.006.00295; Simonds, Donald (Box 6)
  - Some bismuth derivative containing phenyl groups, 1938; UA151.001.006.00296; Dalton, Bradford (Box 6)
  - Preparation of allyl biphenyl and related compounds, 1938; UA151.001.006.00297; Goetz, E. Joseph (Box 6)
  - The design and construction of an inexpensive vacuum tube voltmeter for the measurement of pH values with the glass electrode, 1938; UA151.001.006.00298; Grover, Horace N. (Box 6)
  - Metallography of tin-antimony alloys, 1938; UA151.001.006.00299; Koskela, Urpo (Box 6)
  - The preparation and study of bromo-methyl diphenyl, 1938; UA151.001.006.00300; Newell, Robert L. (Box 6)
  - Study of the bromination of piperonal nitro-methane, 1938; UA151.001.006.00301; Phillips, Arthur P. (Box 6)
  - Nitropentamethyleneoxide, 1938; UA151.001.006.00302; Quinlan, David I. (Box 6)
  - The catalytic oxidation of organic liquids at low temperatures, 1938; UA151.001.006.00303; Ridlon, John (Box 6)
  - The preparation of 2, 4 dinitrophenylhexosazones, 1938; UA151.001.006.00304; Rooney, William Joseph (Box 6)
  - A study of the hydrolysis of alkylated acetoacetic esters, 1938; UA151.001.006.00305; Shand, James E. (Box 6)
  - Preparation and properties of potassium methylamine tartrate, 1938; UA151.001.006.00307; Tekley, Dorothea (Box 6)
  - An improved method for the preparation of p-bromphenylisothiocyanate and the condensation of p-bromphenylisothiocyanate with dibenzoyl methane; and phenylacetonitrile, 1938; UA151.001.006.00308; Turner, Gordon (Box 6)
  - Preparation of b chloro-b' malonyl diethyl ether derivatives of alpha nitro-beta para tolyl ethylene, 1938; UA151.001.006.00309; Willson, Frederic Mayhew (Box 6)
  - Preparation of hexanol 1, 1939; UA151.001.006.00310; Ahearn, William H. Jr. (Box 6)
  - The relation between color and constitution in certain halogenated azo dyes, 1939; UA151.001.006.00311; Arey, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - A study of the physical properties of cutting oils, 1939; UA151.001.006.00312; Baker, Crosby F. Jr. (Box 6)
  - The synthesis of non symetrical di-butyl methyl ketone from the condensation of acetoacetic ester, 1939; UA151.001.006.00313; Baker, Irma (Box 6)
  - The addition of ammonia bases to some new alpha-beta unsaturated nitro compounds, 1939; UA151.001.006.00314; Benington, Frederick (Box 6)
  - Semi-micro analysis, 1939; UA151.001.006.00315; Bowe, Arthur F. (Box 6)
  - Preparation of saccharin and some derivatives of saccharin, 1939; UA151.001.006.00316; Di Matteo, E. Albert (Box 6)
  - A study of the triphenylmethane dyes; malachite green series, 1939; UA151.001.006.00317; Gens, Francis W. (Box 6)
  - The analysis of a white shoe dressing, 1939; UA151.001.006.00318; Ierardi, Paul Nicholas (Box 6)
  - Choline, 1939; UA151.001.006.00319; Kellogg, Marynoyes (Box 6)
  - Methyl, ethyl, and butyl, p-touene sulfonate as alkylating agents with the sodium derivative of nitromethane and malonic ester, 1939; UA151.001.006.00320; Leaffer, M. A. (Box 6)
  - The Wurtz reaction using copper, 1939; UA151.001.006.00321; MacAskill, Norman N. (Box 6)
  - N-butyl naphthalene by the Friedel-Crafts reaction, 1939; UA151.001.006.00322; Manning, Robert N. (Box 6)
  - Preparation of para xenyl carbinol, 1939; UA151.001.006.00323; Morehouse, Clarence K. (Box 6)
  - Studies in metallography, 1939; UA151.001.006.00324; Mounce, William (Box 6)
  - The preparation and properties of various insulatory membranes and the possibility of an electromotive force produced by them, 1939; UA151.001.006.00325; Rubin, Charles V. (Box 6)
  - The condensation of unsaturated aldehydes with nitro methane, 1939; UA151.001.006.00326; Shand, Lloyd D. (Box 6)
  - A study of osazone formation with substituted phenylhydrazines, 1939; UA151.001.006.00327; Shea, Peter P. P. (Box 6)
  - Electrometric titrations in superacid solvents, 1939; UA151.001.006.00328; Troianello, Emilio J. (Box 6)
  - Preparation of triethyl borate, 1939; UA151.001.006.00329; Twombly, John F. (Box 6)
  - Spot test analysis in microchemistry, 1939; UA151.001.006.00330; Wellington, Alline (Box 6)
  - A study of the reaction between adipic acid and paraphenylene diamine, and a general discussion of polymerization, 1940; UA151.001.006.00331; Anderson, Gordon L. (Box 6)
  - A study of the rearrangement of p-acet toluide, 1940; UA151.001.006.00332; Blanchard, W. W. (Box 6)
  - The preparation and direct reduction of p-amino and p-oxy acetophenone, 1940; UA151.001.006.00333; Brown, Joseph E. (Box 6)
  - The properties of cutting oils, 1940; UA151.001.006.00334; Demirjian, Stephen G. (Box 6)
  - A study of cutting oils, 1940; UA151.001.006.00335; Hanson, James H. (Box 6)
  - The Grignard reaction on the ester of an acid, 1940; UA151.001.007.00336; Kazeniac, Stanley (Box 7)
  - Semi-micro quantitative analysis, 1940; UA151.001.007.00337; Marsh, George E. (Box 7)
  - The adaptation of semi-micro technique to the quantitative analysis of ferrous sulphate, 1940; UA151.001.007.00338; Mason, Barbara S. (Box 7)
  - Sulfanilamide, 1940; UA151.001.007.00339; Massello, A. George (Box 7)
  - The condensation of diphenylamine with acetone, 1940; UA151.001.007.00340; Pecheux, Henry Jr. (Box 7)
  - A study of the Wheatstone Bridge for measuring the electrical conductance of electrolytes, 1940; UA151.001.007.00341; Perry, Reginald P. (Box 7)
  - Preparation of azelaic acid and a study of its polyesters, 1940; UA151.001.007.00342; Westervelt, John Dower (Box 7)
  - A course in quantitative analysis, 1941; UA151.001.007.00343; Bettoney, Ethel E. (Box 7)
  - The preparation of sebacic chloride and some of its derivatives, 1941; UA151.001.007.00344; Curtis, Charlotte (Box 7)
  - A study of some special quantitative methods of analysis, 1941; UA151.001.007.00345; McNiff, Katheryn Estelle (Box 7)
  - Reactions with substituted isothiocyanates containing an ester group, 1941; UA151.001.007.00346; Salvo, Charles John (Box 7)
  - Various methods of quantitative analysis, 1941; UA151.001.007.00347; Wells, Justine (Box 7)
  - An attempted preparation of 1-phenyl 3-nitro propene-2 and a qualitative test for the presence of glycine and other alpha-amino acids and a study of certain salts of glycine with organic acids, 1942; UA151.001.007.00348; Barnard, Alfred J. Jr. (Box 7)
  - Etch figures of quartz crystals, 1943; UA151.001.007.00349; Beers, Malcolm (Box 7)
  - The action of biphenyl magnesium bromide on terephthalic aldehyde, 1943; UA151.001.007.00350; Vinci, Alexander S. (Box 7)
  - The electron beam sectrometer, 1943; UA151.001.007.00351; Pitcher, Benjamin A. (Box 7)
  - A quantitative study of the reaction of n-butyl magnesium bromide on heptanone-2, 1943; UA151.001.007.00352; Riley, David W. (Box 7)
  - A study of the nitration of phenothioxin and the structure of the resulting compounds, 1943; UA151.001.007.00353; Thompson, Donald F. (Box 7)
  - Reactions of the Grignard reagent with allyl bromide resulting in the preparation of heptene-1, 1943; UA151.001.007.00354; Williams, W. E. (Box 7)
  - Chlorination of 2 iminouracil 4 acetic acid, 1944; UA151.001.007.00355; Davis, Robert H. (Box 7)
  - The colorimetric determination of beryllium, 1944; UA151.001.007.00356; Herlihy, Mary L. (Box 7)
  - Preparation of p-nitro benzene azo resorcinol and p-nitro benzene azo orcinol and the testing of p-nitro benzene azo orcinol as an indicator for beryllium, 1944; UA151.001.007.00357; Pettigrew, Kathleen (Box 7)
  - A study on choline and its derivatives, 1944; UA151.001.007.00358; Ravin, Herbert A. (Box 7)
  - The x-hydrate of sodium iodide, 1945; UA151.001.007.00359; Asadourian, Anna (Box 7)
  - The spectrophotometer and its use in the determination of fluoride in water, 1945; UA151.001.007.00360; Bliss, Carolyn A. (Box 7)
  - The spectrophotometer and its use in analyzing flourides in water, 1945; UA151.001.007.00361; Brown, Dorothy A. H. (Box 7)
  - The evaluation of perbunan (Buna N) rubber with nitrocellulose as an organic film former, 1945; UA151.001.007.00362; Heilich, Jean (Box 7)
  - Transistion temperatures of sodium iodide, 1945; UA151.001.007.00363; King, Mary P. (Box 7)
  - A study of hexanitrato ammonium cerate reactions for alcohols, 1945; UA151.001.007.00364; Wong, Koon W. (Box 7)
  - Polarographic analysis, 1946; UA151.001.007.00365; Gogan, Thomas F.; Schinkel, Marion (Box 7)
  - Color reaction of boron and quinalizarin, 1946; UA151.001.007.00366; Scott, Barbara J. (Box 7)
  - Halogen derivatives of substituted amino acids, 1946; UA151.001.007.00367; Steeves, Robert W. (Box 7)
  - Preparation of alpha-keto-glutaric acid and of oxal-acetic acid, 1947; UA151.001.007.00368; Ravin, Herbert A. (Box 7)
  - Determination of methyl alcohol in the air, 1948; UA151.001.007.00369; Capobianco, A. G. (Box 7)
  - Preparation of 3-isothiocyanocyclohexene, 1948; UA151.001.007.00370; Howes, Douglas E. Jr. (Box 7)
  - Medicinal calcium compounds with suggestions for clinical trial of two now unused calcium preparations, 1948; UA151.001.007.00371; Schwink, Marjorie (Box 7)
  - A study of the low boiling forerun in the preparation of 1, 2-dibromo-1-ethoxybutane, 1949; UA151.001.007.00372; Graffeo, Michael L. (Box 7)
  - Melting points of solid solutions of benzene and thiophene, 1949; UA151.001.007.00373; Humphrey, Burton G. Jr. (Box 7)
  - 3-Isothiocyanocyclohexene, 1949; UA151.001.007.00374; James, William J. (Box 7)